const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who breaks the news of Mr. Mallard's death?",
        optionA: "Richards",
        optionB: "Josephine",
        optionC: "The Maid",
        optionD: "Brantley",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: 'Identify the figurative language: "She sat with her head thrown back upon the cushion of the chair, quite motionless, except when a sob came up into her throat and shook her, as a child who has cried itself to sleep."',
        optionA: "Metaphor",
        optionB: "Simile",
        optionC: "Personification",
        optionD: "Imagery",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: 'Mrs. Mallard’s cause of death is described as “a joy that kills”. Chopin uses this as final evidence to show that-',
        optionA: "Women were given explicit social rules, and were expected to follow all of them or suffer a tarnished reputation",
        optionB: "All wives were devoted and affectionate towards their husbands",
        optionC: "The pressure of society was so heavy that people were blind to the possibility that conformity could be resisted",
        optionD: "Women were very capable of masking their feelings, which were often very strongly against what society expected of them",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "The delicious breath of rain was in the air... is an example of...",
        optionA: "Metaphor",
        optionB: "Simile",
        optionC: "Personification",
        optionD: "Imagery",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "What did Mrs. mallard believe happened to Mr. Mallard?",
        optionA: "He had had a heart attack",
        optionB: "He had met a road accident",
        optionC: "He had a rail accident",
        optionD: "He had died of illness",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "Her pulses beat fast, and the coursing blood warmed and relaxed every inch of her body is an example of ...",
        optionA: "Imagery",
        optionB: "Irony",
        optionC: "Personification",
        optionD: "Metaphor",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: "What does Josephine believe that Louise is doing behind her closed door?",
        optionA: "She is trying to get over her sadness",
        optionB: "She is killing herself",
        optionC: "She is coping with the reality",
        optionD: "She is listening to music",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "What happens when Louise sees Brently?",
        optionA: "She is overjoyed",
        optionB: "She faints",
        optionC: "She dies",
        optionD: "She screams",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of these is NOT a character in 'The Story of an Hour?'",
        optionA: "Richards",
        optionB: "Brently Mallard",
        optionC: "Josephine",
        optionD: "Kate Chopin",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "What did Louise Mallard usually feel toward her husband during their life together?",
        optionA: "Love",
        optionB: "Anger",
        optionC: "Resentment",
        optionD: "Hatred",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: "What is Richards's relation to Brently?",
        optionA: "Colleague",
        optionB: "Friend",
        optionC: "Neighbour",
        optionD: "Brother",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    }
]
